mytravelmap.tk 2017-12-31

# Privacy policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in privacy law and information security, is an information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.  

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?**

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your Facebook ID or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  

**•** To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. 

**•** To improve our website in order to better serve you. 

**•** To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. 

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like email addresses or credit card numbers.

We do not use Malware Scanning.

We do not use an SSL certificate

**•** We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like email addresses, or credit card numbers. 

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the countries you create on your travel map. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**•** Understand and save user's preferences for future visits. 

**•** Keep track of advertisements. 

**•** Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled. It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

By disabling cookies in your browser, following features might now function properly: 

**•** Logging in through Facebook 

**•** Creating/saving own map 

**•** Sharing map on Facebook wall 

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Advertising Partners**

We use PropellerAds and RevenueHits (Intango) to advertise on our website.

PropellerAds and RevenueHits (Intango), as third-party vendors, use cookies to serve ads on our site which enables them to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet.  

We do not specifically market to children under 13 years of age.

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We don't honor them because the site won't function well without cookies.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking by the Google Analytics or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Last Edited on 18th March, 2016
